i.

+372 58160592

 $oxed{\square}$

sejego@taltech.ee



Tallinn, Estonia



linkedin.com/in/sejego





github.com/sejego



Technical skills

Proficient

Robot Operating System (ROS)

Python

C++

Ruby

UNIX

Git

FIWARE

Microcontrollers Electronics

Solidworks CAD

Familiar

С

Java

VHDL

Ruby on Rails

JavaScript

Docker

Unity Engine

Siemens NX CAD/CAM

NI LabView

Personal skills

Hard-working

Motivated

Organized Team player

Troubleshooting

Time management

Languages

Russian Native English Fluent Estonian Fluent

SERGEI JEGOROV

About

Computer and Systems Engineering MSc student, focusing mainly in the field of robotics, embedded systems, mechatronics. Experienced in operating industrial robots, controllers, as well as ROS-based robots. Interested in improving skills in hardware programming, electronics, and web development. Fond of learning and understanding new things.

Experience

ROS Developer

Tallinn University of Technology | September 2020 | PSG453 research project

- programmed physics of electric drive Digital Twin
- co-authored several research articles on Digital Twin technologies

Mobile Robotics Engineer

Tallinn University of Technology | September 2020 - February 2021 |

- connected mobile robots to Industrial IoT application for handheld devices
- improved mobile robot navigation by connecting NDT matching localization algorithm with native ROS SLAM
- maintained and debugged robots

Development Engineer

IMECC OÜ | July 2018 – July 2019 | L4MS Horizon2020 project

- developed sensor monitoring system for Industrial Logistics IoT platform
- interfaced sensor monitoring system with FIWARE Orion Context Broker
- created an HTTP server that translated custom sensor messages to FIWARE NGSI messages

Education

Higher education

Tallinn University of Technology | 2016 – 2019 | BSc Integrated Engineering

Tallinn University of Technology | 2020 – | MSc Computer and Systems Engineering

Vocational education

Tallinna Tööstushariduskeskus | 2017 – 2018 | Robotics Technician